<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
Author: Kevin Andrea
G00541199
-->


<rooms>
    <room id = "1">
        <title>Clock in the Main Quad</title>
        <description>You are standing in front of the George Mason University Clock.  A plaque on the clock says it was a gift from the Class of 1999.</description>
        <exits>
            <exit id = "NORTH">
                <link>0</link>
                <message>You try to walk north towards the library, but the sidewalk is closed due to construction.</message>
            </exit>
            <exit id = "SOUTH">
                <link>3</link>
                <message>You walk around the grassy median and head south, past the Johnson Center.</message>
            </exit>
            <exit id = "EAST">
                <link>2</link>
                <message>You walk around the fountains as you head towards the statue.</message>
            </exit>
            <exit id = "WEST">
                <link>0</link>
                <message>You try to walk north towards the dorms, however, a large student rally is blocking your path.</message>
            </exit>                        
        </exits>
    </room>
    <room id = "10">
        <title>Shop near the Clock</title>
        <description>You are in the Shop</description>
    </room>
    <room id = "2">
        <title>Mason Statue</title>
        <description>There is a large statue of George Mason resting at the end of the sidewalk. The Mason statue is currently wearing a green Patriots basketball t-shirt.</description>
        <exits>
            <exit id = "NORTH">
                <link>0</link>
                <message>You start to walk north towards the parking deck, but you really don't want to, so you stop yourself.</message>
            </exit>
            <exit id = "SOUTH">
                <link>0</link>
                <message>You try to enter the Johnson Center, but the entrances are closed due to construction.</message>
            </exit>
            <exit id = "WEST">
                <link>1</link>
                <message>You walk around the fountains as you head towards the clock.</message>
            </exit>
            <exit id = "EAST">
                <link>0</link>
                <message>You look to the west and see a very long staircase just past the traffic circle.  You decide against going that direction.</message>
            </exit>                        
        </exits>
    </room> 
    <room id = "3">
        <title>Exploratory Hall</title>
        <description>You are standing out front of the new Exploratory Hall.</description>
        <exits>
            <exit id = "NORTH">
                <link>1</link>
                <message>You head up the sidewalk, towards the clock.</message>
            </exit>
            <exit id = "SOUTH">
                <link>0</link>
                <message>You try to head south, but too many students are smoking near Enterprise hall, so you stay where you are.</message>
            </exit>
            <exit id = "WEST">
                <link>0</link>
                <message>You try to head towards the Johnson Center, but the entrance is closed for construction.</message>
            </exit>
            <exit id = "EAST">
                <link>0</link>
                <message>You look towards Exploratory Hall, but decide to just admire the view from where you are.</message>
            </exit>                        
        </exits>
    </room>     
</rooms>
